morning
아침
Is there any new progress?
새로운 진전이 있나요?
I found this in the lost and found center
분실물 센터에서 이걸 찾았어요
He probably lost it when he ran away.
아마 도망가면서 잃어버렸을 거예요.
Check departure date
출발일 확인
September 5th
9월 5일
The day after Li Yi was killed
리이가 살해된 다음날
I doubt Yin Tianhong’s ultimate goal
나는 Yin Tianhong의 최종 목표를 의심합니다.
Itu Li Yi
이투 리 이
if we hadn't met you
우리가 당신을 만나지 않았다면
Maybe he has escaped from Xiyuan
어쩌면 그는 Xiyuan에서 탈출했을 수도 있습니다
So this is illegal forgery
그럼 불법 위조네요
You will also need to check with the ferry company.
페리 회사에도 확인이 필요합니다.
Strange things
이상한 것들
Is this our company's certificate?
이게 우리 회사의 인증서인가요?
but
하지만
There is no one named Liang Ren here.
여기에는 Liang Ren이라는 사람이 없습니다.
September 5th
9월 5일
Destination: Donggang
목적지: 동강
We suspect there's someone aboard the Desire
Desire 호에는 누군가가 탑승한 것으로 의심됩니다.
Help smuggle the robots to Donggang
로봇을 동강으로 밀수입하는 것을 도와주세요
this
이것
Has the ship arrived?
배가 도착했나요?
I want to meet the captain
캡틴을 만나고 싶어요
Just shipped it a few days ago
며칠전에 배송됐네요
The captain also called him.
선장도 그에게 전화를 걸었습니다.
Xiao Li, please ask Captain Jiang to come to the office.
Xiao Li 씨, Jiang 선장에게 사무실로 와달라고 부탁하세요.
Lao Chiang, both of them are smart investigators.
Lao Chiang, 둘 다 똑똑한 수사관입니다.
Captain, I tell you the truth.
선장님, 사실대로 말하겠습니다.
We suspect someone is using your cargo ship for smuggling
누군가가 당신의 화물선을 이용해 밀수를 하고 있는 것으로 의심됩니다.
No, are you mistaken?
아니, 착각하신 건가요?
Is this your ship number?
이것이 귀하의 선박 번호입니까?
of
~의
Have you met this person?
이 사람을 만나본 적 있나요?
No
아니요
How many times have you gone to sea this year?
올해 바다에 몇 번이나 가셨나요?
This is the tenth time this month, right?
이번달로 열번째죠?
Have you noticed anything unusual during this time?
이 기간 동안 특이한 점을 발견하셨나요?
In fact, in January this year
실제로 올해 1월에는
Something happened in the nearby waters
근처 바다에서 무슨 일이 일어났어요
I don't know what case you want to investigate
어떤 사건을 조사하고 싶은지 모르겠어요
Is there any contact?
연락은 있나요?
what do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
There are unapproved foreign cargo ships
승인되지 않은 외국 화물선이 있습니다
Sailing towards Xiyuan waters
시위안(Xiyuan) 해역으로 항해
As a result, he was arrested by the beach police
그 결과 그는 해변 경찰에 체포됐다.
Everyone on the boat wanted to escape
배에 탄 사람들은 모두 탈출을 원했습니다.
However, the storm at sea that day was very violent.
그러나 그날 바다의 폭풍은 매우 격렬했습니다.
many people drowned
많은 사람이 익사했다
Later, while examining the body that washed up on the beach,
이후 해변에 떠내려온 시신을 조사하던 중,
It turns out they are all robots
알고보니 다 로봇이네
This even made the news
이게 뉴스에도 나왔는데
I have the impression
인상이 있어요
You two, can you stop?
너희 둘, 그만 둘 수 있겠니?
Don't worry, we'll keep it a secret
걱정하지 마세요. 비밀로 할게요.
Thanks
감사해요
Very good, very good
아주 좋아, 아주 좋아
But you better check it out
하지만 확인해 보는 게 좋을 거야
eager crew
열정적인 승무원
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me
질문이 있으시면 언제든지 저에게 연락해주세요.
Definitely good
확실히 좋아
where are we going now
우리 지금 어디로 가는 거야?
night market
야시장
Why go to the night market?
야시장에 왜 가나요?
Very close to the pier
부두와 매우 가까움
Many sailors often go there to eat
많은 선원들이 식사하러 자주 갑니다.
I have a friend who does business there
거기에서 사업하는 친구가 있어요
Let's ask him first
그 사람에게 먼저 물어보자
Boss
사장
Cheng Nuo
쳉 누오
Now, wait a minute
자, 잠깐만요
I'm very busy today
오늘은 매우 바빠요
there are many people today
오늘은 사람이 많아요
sit, sit, sit
앉아, 앉아, 앉아
He is Sun Yao
그는 쑨야오이다
my high school classmates
내 고등학교 동창들
Enter the society after graduation
졸업 후 사회에 진출하다
he is a sailor
그는 선원이다
sailor
선원
It pops up when I think of it
생각하면 떠오르네요
Initially, the sailors did their job well
처음에는 선원들이 일을 잘했습니다.
I had no choice but to come to the night market to set up a stall.
어쩔 수 없이 야시장에 와서 노점을 차렸습니다.
I don't know how much longer I can hold on.
얼마나 더 버틸 수 있을지 모르겠습니다.
Sun Yao, what are you doing?
쑨야오, 뭐 하는 거야?
Come, come, come
오세요, 오세요, 오세요
Come quickly
빨리 오세요
I am coming
나는 온다
who are you chatting with?
누구랑 채팅 중이야?
no one no one
아무도 아무도
home home
가정 가정
this is my boyfriend
이 사람은 내 남자친구야
colleague
동료
By the way, this time I want to ask you
그런데 이번에는 당신에게 묻고 싶습니다.
Have you met this person?
이 사람을 만나본 적 있나요?
no effect
효과 없음
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
correct
옳은
Our class will have a party tomorrow
우리 반은 내일 파티를 열 거야
are you going?
가는거야?
Busy with work
일이 바빠
No matter how busy you are, you have to go
아무리 바빠도 가야 해
You haven't attended a class reunion in several years.
당신은 몇 년 동안 동창회에 참석하지 않았습니다.
I really can't leave
난 정말 떠날 수 없어
real
진짜
No matter what happens tomorrow
내일 무슨 일이 일어나더라도
you must be there
당신은 거기에 있어야합니다
Something important needs to be announced
중요한 내용을 발표해야 합니다.
The girl next to me is nice
내 옆에 있는 여자는 착해요
What to eat slowly?
천천히 뭐 먹을까?
Does this have anything to do with women?
이것이 여성과 관련이 있습니까?
what does he want to announce
그 사람은 무엇을 발표하고 싶어 하는 걸까
It must be related to women
반드시 여성과 관련이 있어야 합니다.
How could he say it himself?
그가 어떻게 직접 말할 수 있었습니까?
I am a thousand-year-old prodigal who cannot be bound.
나는 얽매일 수 없는 천세 탕자입니다.
Look at the towel around his neck
목에 감긴 수건 좀 봐
There are cartoon patterns on it
그것에 만화 패턴이 있습니다
Are there still stickers on the cups?
컵에 아직도 스티커가 붙어있나요?
only
오직
He just lowered his head when replying to the message
그 사람은 메시지에 답하면서 고개를 숙였을 뿐인데
Still smiling
아직도 웃고 있다
You'd better go to the party tomorrow
내일 파티에 가는 게 좋겠다
We rarely have real friends
우리는 진짜 친구가 거의 없다
Eat quickly. I'll take you home after you're done.
빨리 먹어요. 끝나면 집에 데려다줄게요.
I'm not hungry, so I'll go back first.
배고프지 않으니 먼저 돌아가겠습니다.
Who created me?
나를 창조한 사람은 누구인가?
What was my first obsession?
나의 첫 집착은 무엇이었는가?
The period after being raided brightly
밝게 습격당한 후의 기간
In the end what happened
결국 무슨 일이 일어났나
Why
왜
my memory will be in pieces
내 기억은 산산조각이 나겠지
Cheng Nuo heard that you are now working in Mingmo.
Cheng Nuo는 당신이 현재 Mingmo에서 일하고 있다는 소식을 들었습니다.
How difficult is it to work there?
그곳에서 일하는 것이 얼마나 어려운가요?
The income should be high, right?
소득이 높아야겠죠?
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
go! go! go
가다! 가다! 가다
In what situations would you refuse to be assertive?
어떤 상황에서 당신은 자기 주장을 거부하겠습니까?
your girlfriend
당신의 여자 친구
When did it happen
언제 그런 일이 일어났나요?
five or six months ago
5~6개월 전
Think about it, this is my best friend
생각해봐, 이게 내 가장 친한 친구야
halo
후광
Cheng Nuo
쳉 누오
Too much
너무 많은
let me introduce you to
에게 당신을 소개 할게요
introduce
소개하다
Come on, hurry up
자, 서둘러
let me tell you something
너에게 뭐 하나 알려 줄께
Today is our class reunion
오늘은 우리 동창회야
Use this opportunity
이 기회를 활용하세요
I want to share happy things with you
행복한 것들을 여러분과 나누고 싶습니다
happiness
행복
I have been wandering at sea for five years
나는 5년 동안 바다를 헤매고 있었습니다
I really didn't expect that I would go ashore
나는 내가 해변에 갈 것이라고 정말로 기대하지 않았습니다
never thought about it
그것에 대해 생각해본 적이 없어
i can come up with an idea
내가 아이디어를 생각해 낼 수 있어요
how are you today?
오늘 기분이 어떠세요?
we are together too
우리도 함께야
Day 184
184일차
Marry me in one thought
한 생각에 나랑 결혼해
marry him
그와 결혼
Promise to marry me in one year
1년 뒤에 나랑 결혼하자고 약속해줘
kiss a
키스하다
halo
후광
Hello, are you Mr. Cheng Nuo?
안녕하세요. Cheng Nuo 씨이신가요?
I'm the person in charge of Channel Ferry
채널페리 담당자입니다
we found something
우리가 뭔가를 찾았어요
Is it convenient for you to come here now?
지금 여기 오는 것이 편리합니까?
Okay, I'll be there in a minute
알았어, 금방 갈게
sorry
죄송합니다
I even called you on the weekends
주말에도 전화했는데
Why are you being polite to me?
왜 나한테 예의바르게 굴어?
thank you for the tea
차 고마워요
Then I'll just say it
그럼 그냥 말할게요
Kasus Chen Xinhui
카수스 첸 신후이
Why did you want to come to me?
왜 나한테 오려고 했어?
Why did you suddenly think of asking this?
왜 갑자기 이런 질문을 하려고 생각했나요?
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
After working for a while
잠시 일한 후
I seem to suddenly understand
문득 이해가 되는 것 같아
Your initial confusion and feelings are gone
초기의 혼란과 감정은 사라졌습니다
I remember the beginning
시작을 기억해요
I read your article
나는 당신의 기사를 읽었습니다
Child Psychology Paper
아동 심리학 논문
It's mentioned in it
그 내용에 언급되어 있어요
How to remind a traumatized child
상처받은 아이에게 상기시키는 방법
open your heart again
다시 마음을 열어라
according to me
나에 따라
You may have several different ideas
여러 가지 생각이 있을 수 있습니다.
what is it? Is your work not going well lately?
그것은 무엇입니까? 요즘 일이 잘 안 되시나요?
No
아니요
excuse me
실례합니다
How did we first meet?
우리는 어떻게 처음 만났나요?
I went back to school to give a speech
나는 연설을 하기 위해 학교로 돌아갔다
after the lecture
강의가 끝난 후
Come and ask me some questions
와서 나에게 몇 가지 질문을 물어보세요
So at this time we
그래서 이때 우리는
Contact established
연락처가 설정되었습니다.
Do not you remember
기억나지 않나요?
You're not a robot, are you?
당신은 로봇이 아니죠?
joke
농담
a bit strange
조금 이상하다
Cheng Nuo also asked me the same question recently
Cheng Nuo도 최근에 나에게 같은 질문을 했습니다.
Ask how we met
우리가 어떻게 만났는지 물어보세요
Why do I suggest you go to improve your eyesight?
시력을 개선하기 위해 가라고 제안하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Yes
예
Why is he asking you these questions?
그 사람이 왜 당신에게 이런 질문을 하는 걸까요?
I don't know either
나도 모르겠어요
perhaps
아마도
He wants to know more about his partner
그는 파트너에 대해 더 알고 싶어합니다.
this is information
이것은 정보입니다
This Xu Miao is the chief pursuer on the ship.
이 Xu Miao는 배의 주요 추적자입니다.
Entry-exit joint inspection of crew life
승무원 생활 출입 합동점검
He is responsible for everything, including finances.
그는 재정을 포함한 모든 것을 책임집니다.
What happened to these two complaints in early July?
7월 초에 이 두 건의 민원은 어떻게 됐나요?
Last year, a crew member complained that he was withholding his quarterly bonus.
작년에 한 승무원이 분기별 보너스를 보류하고 있다고 불평했습니다.
and food subsidies
그리고 식량 보조금
But Xu Miao thinks
하지만 Xu Miao는 생각합니다.
It was the other party who violated company regulations first.
먼저 회사 규정을 위반한 것은 상대방이었다.
This is not a reduction, but a penalty.
이는 감소가 아니라 벌금입니다.
How do companies ultimately identify them?
기업은 궁극적으로 이를 어떻게 식별합니까?
The problem lies here
문제는 여기에 있다
Staff questions
직원 질문
We must check it out
우리는 그것을 확인해야합니다
But Xu Miao has a strong sense of self-esteem
하지만 Xu Miao는 자존감이 강해요
He said I didn't trust him and wouldn't let me see his watch.
그는 내가 그를 믿지 않으며 그의 시계를 보지 못하게 하겠다고 말했습니다.
He even quarreled with me
그 사람은 나랑 말다툼까지 했어
I was just suspicious
나는 단지 의심스러웠다.
Is this a misuse of public funds?
이것은 공적 자금을 오용하는 것입니까?
That's why I'm not allowed to look at my watch.
그래서 시계를 보면 안 돼요.
So what to do in the end?
그래서 결국 무엇을 해야 할까요?
When it comes to quarter-end accounting,
분기말 회계를 보면,
The numbers are exactly the same.
숫자는 정확히 동일합니다.
Xu Miao probably felt that the company was suspicious of him.
Xu Miao는 아마도 회사가 자신을 의심하고 있다고 느꼈을 것입니다.
I feel a little uncomfortable
좀 불편한 것 같아요
He resigned soon after
그는 곧 사임했다.
Yes, that's the problem
응, 그게 문제야
I also talked to all the staff
직원들한테도 다 얘기했는데
In fact, a similar incident occurred only once last year.
실제로 비슷한 사건은 지난해 딱 한 번 발생했다.
Where does Xu Miao work now?
Xu Miao는 지금 어디에서 일합니까?
He no longer goes to sea
그는 더 이상 바다에 가지 않는다
maybe you want to take a break
어쩌면 넌 좀 쉬고 싶을지도 몰라
Do you have any influence on this person?
당신은 이 사람에게 어떤 영향을 미치나요?
he is a fan
그는 팬이다
There seemed to be nothing else going on.
더 이상 아무 일도 일어나지 않는 것 같았습니다.
halo
후광
Sorry, something just happened
죄송합니다. 방금 문제가 발생했습니다.
Any new clues?
새로운 단서가 있나요?
Lang Ning's former chief of staff Xu Miao is very suspicious.
Lang Ning의 전 참모장 Xu Miao는 매우 의심 스럽습니다.
I suspect he lost money gambling
내 생각엔 그 사람이 도박으로 돈을 잃은 것 같아
That's why we embezzled public funds
이래서 공금을 횡령했구나
This hole can be filled later
이 구멍은 나중에 채울 수 있습니다
He was probably smuggled in with him.
그는 아마도 그와 함께 밀수입되었을 것입니다.
I'll send you the address
주소 보내드릴게요
Let's meet there
거기서 만나자
How's it going
어떻게되고 있습니까
listen
듣다
Who are you looking for?
당신은 누구를 찾고 있나요?
Is your name Xu Miao?
당신의 이름이 Xu Miao 입니까?
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
I heard you can help people leave Xiyuan City
사람들이 Xiyuan City를 떠나도록 도울 수 있다고 들었습니다.
Who do you listen to?
누구의 말을 듣나요?
If there's no problem, leave quickly
문제없으면 빨리 나가세요
This is your betting history on sports betting sites
스포츠 베팅 사이트의 베팅 내역입니다.
How do you make up for losing so much?
그렇게 많은 것을 잃은 것을 어떻게 만회합니까?
If we go in now, we still have to talk.
지금 들어가면 아직 얘기를 해야 해요.
If not, see you at the police station
안되면 경찰서에서 만나요
I don't understand what you are talking about
무슨 말인지 이해가 안 돼요
Okay, then don't regret it
알았어, 그럼 후회하지 마
There will soon be evidence
곧 증거가 나오겠죠
Incorrect
잘못된
Wait a moment
잠깐만요
that's right
좋아요
When I was at the beginning of the year
제가 연초였을 때
i lost a lot of money
나는 돈을 많이 잃었다
At first I thought about using the spare money on the boat to make money.
처음에는 배에 남은 돈으로 돈을 벌까 생각도 했습니다.
I didn't expect it to end
끝날 줄은 몰랐어
All discounted
모두 할인됨
So you take people to smuggle
그래서 사람들을 밀수하러 데려가는군요
What do you want to know?
무엇을 알고 싶나요?
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
i know this person
나는 이 사람을 안다
I was waiting for him at the dock that day
나는 그날 부두에서 그를 기다리고 있었다
He didn't show up in the end
그 사람은 결국 나타나지 않았어
The order was finally empty.
드디어 주문이 비었습니다.
Where do you find these customers?
이러한 고객을 어디서 찾을 수 있나요?
Clients and Perjury
의뢰인과 위증
This is all provided by Brother Biao
이것은 모두 Biao 형제가 제공한 것입니다.
Then didn't he follow Brother Biao's path?
그렇다면 그는 Biao 형제의 길을 따르지 않았습니까?
Brother Biao is the biggest black fish
Biao 형제는 가장 큰 검은 물고기입니다.
Smuggling channels throughout Taiyuan
타이위안 전역의 밀수 경로
Everything is in Brother Biao's hands
모든 것이 Biao 형제의 손에 달려 있습니다
Others also want to do it
다른 사람들도 해보고 싶어
You must also have courage.
용기도 있어야 합니다.
The smuggling route that my partner and I developed ourselves
나와 파트너가 직접 개발한 밀수 루트
This also requires Brother Biao’s approval.
이 역시 뱌오 형제의 승인이 필요합니다.
working normally
정상적으로 작동
Mitra
미트라
You have accomplices
공범이 있어요
He was the first to suggest smuggling.
그는 밀수를 제안한 첫 번째 사람이었습니다.
He is also the one who contacted Brother Biao
뱌오 형제에게 연락한 사람이기도 하다.
I'm responsible for getting people on board.
나는 사람들을 탑승시키는 일을 담당하고 있습니다.
Is he also a cast member?
그 사람도 출연진인가요?
He is my former colleague
그 사람은 내 전 동료야
What's his name
무슨 일이 그의 이름이다
If I tell you, will the sin be lessened?
내가 말하면 죄가 줄어들겠습니까?
Do you want to say it or not?
말하고 싶은가, 말고 싶은가?
he is
그는
Sun Yao
쑨 야오
Could you repeat that
다시 말씀해 주시겠어요?
What is he doing
그는 무엇을 하고 있나요?
He recently opened a stall at the Fukou Night Market.
그는 최근 후코우 야시장에 노점을 열었습니다.
I want to talk to Sun Yao alone
쑨야오와 단둘이 얘기하고 싶어
Although he is a bit impetuous
그 사람이 좀 성급하긴 하지만
But I still understand the big picture.
그러나 나는 여전히 큰 그림을 이해합니다.
it's not supposed to do anything like that
그런 짓은 하면 안 돼
Then I'll leave first
그럼 나 먼저 갈게
An Qiu, let’s go first
안추야, 먼저 가자
until tomorrow
내일까지
morning
아침
How did we first meet?
우리는 어떻게 처음 만났나요?
Cheng Nuo also asked me the same question recently
Cheng Nuo도 최근에 나에게 같은 질문을 했습니다.
he drank too much
그 사람은 너무 많이 마셨어
Cheng Nuo
쳉 누오
Why did you come?
왜 왔나요?
too late
너무 늦었어
I drank three bottles later.
나중에는 세 병을 마셨다.
let me give you new chopsticks
새 젓가락 줄게
sit here
여기 앉으세요
let's talk
얘기하자
It's okay, keep going, keep going
괜찮아, 계속해, 계속해
Coming soon
곧 출시 예정
Come here quickly
빨리 여기로 와
Why are you so serious?
뭐가 그리 심각해?
I found someone today
오늘 누군가를 찾았어요
Namanya Xu Miao
나만야 쉬 미아오
You know him, right?
그 사람 알지?
I know my former colleagues
나는 내 전 동료들을 안다.
We will no longer contact you after this.
이 이후에는 더 이상 연락하지 않습니다.
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
Xu Miao took advantage of his position to lead people to smuggle
Xu Miao는 자신의 지위를 이용하여 사람들을 밀수꾼으로 이끌었습니다.
He also provided a person
사람도 주더군요
that is you
그건 너야
How could he talk nonsense?
어떻게 말도 안되는 소리를 할 수 있니?
Xu Miao also said
쉬미아오도 말했다.
You initiated all the smuggling.
당신은 모든 밀수를 시작했습니다.
Customers are also arranged by you
고객도 당신이 준비합니다
Impossible Cheng Nuo
임파서블 쳉 누오
So, you haven’t done what I said.
그래서 당신은 내가 말한 것을 이행하지 않았습니다.
No
아니요
Coming for both of you
두 분 모두를 위해 오세요
Thank you for giving it to me.
나에게 주셔서 감사합니다.
This person was originally going to board Xu Miao's ship
이 사람은 원래 Xu Miao의 배에 탑승하려고했습니다.
Leaving Saiyuan
사이위안 출발
I suspect he had something to do with my mother's death
그 사람이 내 어머니의 죽음과 관련이 있는 것 같아요
you really don't know
당신은 정말로 모른다
Why smuggling?
밀수를 하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
I need money
난 돈이 필요
You know, I'm getting married soon
있잖아, 나 곧 결혼할 거야
I want to give him a good home
나는 그에게 좋은 집을 주고 싶다
I do this business
나는 이 사업을 한다
You can't make money
당신은 돈을 벌 수 없습니다
What if I have children in the future?
나중에 아이가 생긴다면 어떻게 될까요?
How can I support this family?
이 가족을 어떻게 부양할 수 있나요?
You are the first person to say this
이런 말을 한 사람은 당신이 처음이에요
Our own sailors have to be out there all year round.
우리 선원들은 일년 내내 그곳에 있어야 합니다.
that's why i do it
그게 내가 하는 이유야
Now I feel like my income is not enough.
이제 내 수입이 충분하지 않은 것 같습니다.
Are they forcing you to buy a house or asking for an engagement gift?
집을 사라고 강요하거나 약혼 선물을 요구하나요?
Besides, why didn't you tell me you had no money?
게다가 왜 돈이 없다고 나에게 말하지 않았나요?
don't tell other students
다른 학생들에게 말하지 마세요
I don't want to owe you anything
나는 당신에게 아무것도 빚지고 싶지 않습니다
tell me about this person
이 사람에 대해 말해줘
I don't know how to find my customers
고객을 찾는 방법을 모르겠습니다.
Who is he?
그는 누구입니까?
Does anyone know why we left Sai Yuan?
우리가 Sai Yuan을 떠난 이유를 아는 사람 있나요?
Only Brother Biao knows
오직 뱌오 형제만이 알고 있다
He gave a false identity
그는 거짓 신분을 밝혔습니다
he is a wanted criminal
그 사람은 수배범이야
Be careful
조심하세요
But I've never seen it with my own eyes
하지만 난 내 눈으로 본 적이 없어
Cheng Nuo
쳉 누오
You won't give up on me just like that, will you?
당신은 나를 그렇게 포기하지 않을 것입니다, 그렇죠?
Don't you plan to get married?
결혼할 생각은 없나요?
Thanks
감사해요
Does your fiancé know?
약혼자도 알고 있나요?
i never told him
난 그 사람한테 말한 적 없어
Don't do similar things again in the future
앞으로는 비슷한 짓 하지 마세요
This is very irresponsible behavior on his part
이는 그 사람의 매우 무책임한 행동이다.
You said it yourself
직접 말했잖아
Finally have a home
드디어 집이 생겼다
What would he do if you went to jail?
당신이 감옥에 가면 그 사람은 어떻게 할까요?
Appreciating the talent in front of you is the most important thing
눈앞에 있는 재능을 평가하는 것이 가장 중요하다
How is your friend?
친구는 잘 지내요?
It's none of his business
그건 그 사람이 상관할 일이 아니야
What we're looking for is the smuggler leader.
우리가 찾고 있는 사람은 밀수꾼 두목이에요.
just to find it
그냥 찾으려고
Confirm the source of the fake identity
가짜 신원의 출처를 확인하세요
I asked the second team to investigate the specific situation
구체적인 상황에 대해 2차팀에 조사를 의뢰했습니다
Zhou Chen in the Android smuggling case
안드로이드 밀수 사건의 저우첸
get some information
정보를 좀 얻으세요
I gonna go see
보러 갈게
Here's a June report on Android smuggling
Android 밀수에 관한 6월 보고서는 다음과 같습니다.
According to our understanding
우리의 이해에 따르면
Xie Wenbiao and his two younger brothers were on the boat at that time
당시 배에는 Xie Wenbiao와 그의 두 남동생이 타고 있었습니다.
By the way, Brother Biao’s real name is Xie Wenbiao
참고로 뱌오 형제의 본명은 셰원뱌오(Xie Wenbiao)입니다.
The smuggling ship is about to enter the port.
밀항선이 항구에 입항하려고 합니다.
As a result, I saw law enforcement officers conducting surprise inspections at the docks.
그 결과 법집행관들이 부두에서 기습 점검을 하는 모습을 목격했습니다.
Xie Wenbiao saw no way to escape
Xie Wenbiao는 탈출할 방법을 찾지 못했습니다.
He forced seven robots to jump into the sea with him
그는 7대의 로봇을 자신과 함께 바다에 뛰어들도록 강요했습니다.
he did run away
그 사람은 도망갔어
All robots will sink
모든 로봇은 가라앉을 것이다
Can't robots swim?
로봇은 수영을 할 수 없나요?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
But we did an autopsy
하지만 부검을 해보니
Discover the bionic human body
생체 공학적 인체를 발견해보세요
There is a large amount of anesthetic residue
마취잔류량이 많아
Is giving the medicine first to facilitate transportation?
운송을 용이하게 하기 위해 약을 먼저 투여하는 것입니까?
Yes, they thought they could get ashore.
예, 그들은 해변에 도착할 수 있다고 생각했습니다.
Just wake up android
그냥 일어나 안드로이드
Who knew we would encounter a law enforcement boat?
우리가 법 집행 보트를 만날 줄 누가 알았겠습니까?
All the robots are sleeping.
모든 로봇이 자고 있습니다.
Just jump into the sea
그냥 바다에 뛰어들어라
Although I can swim
수영을 할 수는 있지만
The chance of survival is also very small
생존 가능성도 매우 낮음
only six bodies
시체가 여섯 개밖에 없어
It's still us
아직 우리야
It took more than a week to find
찾는데 일주일 넘게 걸렸다
The other may have been swept away by the current.
다른 하나는 조류에 휩쓸려 갔을 수도 있습니다.
Why did you suddenly think of asking about this case?
왜 갑자기 이 사건에 대해 물어볼 생각을 하게 되었나요?
Any new clues?
새로운 단서가 있나요?
This has nothing to do with this case
이번 사건과는 관련이 없습니다
Kami mencari Xie Wenbiao
카미 멘카리 시에원비아오
He and the robot we are looking for
그와 우리가 찾고 있는 로봇
Contacted
연락함
By the way, do you know it exists?
그건 그렇고, 그것이 존재한다는 것을 알고 있습니까?
He has just been arrested by the police and is being interrogated
그는 최근 경찰에 체포돼 심문을 받고 있다.
Prepare to eliminate smuggling gangs
밀수 갱단을 제거할 준비를 하세요.
Not yet announced
아직 발표되지 않음
So don’t share it with others for now
그러니 지금은 다른 사람과 공유하지 마세요.
very good
매우 좋은
take me to see him
나를 데리고 그를 만나러 가세요
Is this a request or a command?
이것은 부탁인가, 명령인가?
help
돕다
Xiaodong went to contact him.
Xiaodong이 그에게 연락하러 갔다.
If you have anything to ask, please let me know.
문의하실 사항이 있으시면 알려주시기 바랍니다.
Did you arrange this order?
이 순서를 정하셨나요?
Who contacted you at that time?
그때 누가 연락했습니까?
Is this the man in the photo?
이 사람이 사진 속 남자인가요?
That should be him
그 사람이어야 해
I only talked to him on the phone
그 사람하고는 전화로만 얘기했어요
Did he say that?
그가 그렇게 말했나요?
Why give up Saiyuan?
왜 Saiyuan을 포기합니까?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
At that time, this order had not yet been issued to this person.
당시 이 명령은 아직 이 사람에게 발부되지 않았습니다.
I said I won't remember it wrong
내가 잘못 기억하지 않을 거라고 말했어
I gave it to Sun Yao like this
순야오에게 이렇게 줬어요
The woman upstairs is still alive
위층 여자는 아직 살아있어요
What
무엇
I asked the woman if she was still alive
나는 그 여자에게 아직 살아 있느냐고 물었다.
There are indeed living robots.
실제로 살아있는 로봇이 있습니다.
You made it very clear
아주 명확하게 해주셨네요
Is this girl a robot?
이 여자는 로봇인가요?
The boat I was on
내가 탔던 배
If I encounter a law enforcement ship, wouldn't I be unlucky?
법 집행 선박을 만나면 운이 좋지 않을까요?
If not, my order
그렇지 않다면 내 주문은
Su Zhouchen
쑤저우첸
The day after the smuggling incident
밀수 사건 다음날
Have you checked Sun Yao’s family?
Sun Yao의 가족을 확인해 보셨나요?
In the end, people are still missed.
결국 사람들은 여전히 ​​그리워하고 있습니다.
Wanbu
완부
I'm very sorry
나는 매우 미안 해요
This time I neglected my duty.
이번에는 의무를 소홀히 했습니다.
But now the evidence is compelling
하지만 이제 증거는 설득력이 있습니다
You can ask Xu for proof of identity.
Xu에게 신원 증명을 요청할 수 있습니다.
Cheng Nuo
쳉 누오
This time, the three of you will lead a team to collect evidence.
이번에는 세 사람이 팀을 이끌고 증거 수집을 하게 됩니다.
A second team will work with you
두 번째 팀이 귀하와 협력할 것입니다.
Wanbu
완부
Okay, that's it.
알았어, 그게 다야.
The report must also be submitted to the Immigration Service
보고서는 출입국 관리소에도 제출되어야 합니다.
Must be done well
잘해야 해
You all go
너희 모두 가거라
minister
장관
I said it was solved
해결됐다고 했더니
halo
후광
this is me
이게 나야
tomorrow
내일
Do you want to come along?
같이 가실래요?
No
아니요
us
우리를
haven't seen you for a long time
오랫동안 당신을 보지 못했어요
I should have noticed
눈치챘어야 했는데
Sun Yao ingin melindungi Xu Yinian
Sun Yao ingin melindungi Xu Yinian
That's why you've been hiding it from me
그래서 나한테 숨긴 거야
do you feel anxious
불안해?
Sun Yao ditipu oleh Xu Yinian
Sun Yao는 Xu Yinian과 함께했습니다.
Still thinking about how to arrest someone?
아직도 누군가를 체포하는 방법을 생각하고 있나요?
I saw they complied
나는 그들이 준수하는 것을 보았다
I believe Xu Nianniian’s feelings for Sun Yao
나는 Sun Yao에 대한 Xu Nianniian의 감정을 믿습니다.
that's right
좋아요
I just don't know
난 그냥 모르겠어요
How should I talk to Sun Yao?
Sun Yao와 어떻게 대화해야 하나요?
Dimana Xu Yinian?
디마나 쉬이니안?
he is not at home
그 사람은 집에 없어요
Sun Yao
쑨 야오
Come this time
이번에 오세요
I know, I know you will come this time
알아요 이번에는 올 거라는 걸 알아요
What do you want to ask?
무엇을 묻고 싶나요?
Sorry, I lied to you
미안, 내가 거짓말을 했어
How did you know each other
어떻게 서로를 알았나요?
Weak start to the year
올해의 시작이 약함
only a few guests
손님이 몇 ​​명 안 되니
I drank a lot of wine alone that day
그 날 나 혼자 와인을 많이 마셨어
get up
일어나
This is where
이곳은
my house
우리집
You passed out on the beach, don't get me wrong.
당신은 해변에서 기절했습니다. 오해하지 마세요.
The following are the recent messages this site has received
다음은 이 사이트가 받은 최근 메시지입니다.
Smuggling incident near Taiyuan Beach
타이위안 해변 인근 밀수 사건
It is understood that the cargo ship carries several robots
화물선에는 여러 대의 로봇이 실려 있는 것으로 파악된다.
Is Sun Yao at home?
Sun Yao는 집에 있나요?
Sun Yao
쑨 야오
Is Sun Yao here?
쑨야오가 여기 있어요?
Zai Zai Zai
자이 자이 자이
You are Sun Yao
당신은 순 야오입니다
Canaan
가나안 땅
There's something I want to know from you.
당신에게 알고 싶은 것이 있습니다.
Did you go to the beach this morning?
오늘 아침에 해변에 가셨나요?
Some fishermen saw you drinking on the beach
어떤 어부들이 당신이 해변에서 술을 마시는 것을 보았습니다.
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
You just need to answer yes or no
예, 아니오로만 대답하면 됩니다.
visited
방문했다
Have you ever seen anyone suspicious?
의심스러운 사람을 본 적이 있나요?
No
아니요
No special circumstances
특별한 사정은 없습니다
No, I was the only one drinking beer.
아니, 맥주를 마시는 사람은 나뿐이었다.
Go home and sleep
집에 가서 자요
Who else is in your family?
가족 중에 또 누가 있나요?
my sweetheart
내 연인
He doesn't feel well today
그 사람 오늘 몸이 안 좋아
I fell asleep just after taking the medicine
약먹고 바로 잠들었어요
How do you feel looking back?
돌아보면 어떤 기분이 드나요?
Remember to contact us
저희에게 연락하는 것을 잊지 마세요
Thanks
감사해요
OK
좋아요
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I want to repay you
보답하고 싶어
You don't have to pay me back
나한테 돈을 갚을 필요는 없어
That's not why I saved you
내가 널 구한 건 그게 아니야
use use
사용 사용
can I ask you a question
질문해도 될까요
Are you a robot?
당신은 로봇입니까?
you
너
you can say it slowly
천천히 말해도 돼
I transferred to Saiyuan
사이위안으로 옮겼어요
I heard it was because someone offered a high price.
누군가가 높은 가격을 제시했기 때문이라고 들었습니다.
Come and buy from us
와서 우리에게서 구입하세요
We spent a few days at sea
우리는 바다에서 며칠을 보냈어요
Waiting to go ashore
해변으로 가기를 기다리고 있어요
Unexpectedly, I became the target of others.
뜻밖에도 나는 다른 사람들의 표적이 되었다.
The stowaways asked us to jump into the sea and escape
밀항자들은 우리에게 바다에 뛰어들어 탈출하라고 했습니다
he said if he was caught
그 사람이 만약 잡히면 말했지
we will die
우리는 죽을 것이다
My original obsession was to make my master happy
나의 원래 집착은 주인님을 기쁘게 해드리는 것이었습니다.
Cannot refuse any request from the master
주인의 어떤 요구도 거절할 수 없다
Quick to use
빠른 사용
Namaku Xu Yinian
나마쿠 쉬이니안
My name is Sun Yao
내 이름은 쑨야오예요
you were a sailor
당신은 선원이었어
It must be fun to be a sailor, right?
선원이 되는 건 재미있겠죠?
happy
행복하다
Sailors just run around
선원들은 그냥 돌아다녀
Go to various places to eat various seafood
다양한 해산물을 먹으러 여러 곳을 가보세요
Anyway, my family is gone
어쨌든 우리 가족은 사라졌어요
Don't worry
괜찮아요
Wherever I go, it's home
어딜가든 집이네
I am
그래요
can i be your family
내가 당신의 가족이 될 수 있나요
After Xu and I were together for a year,
Xu와 내가 1년 동안 함께한 후,
I also have a start
나도 시작이 있어
The most important thing is that he gave me a home
가장 중요한 것은 그가 나에게 집을 주었다는 것입니다
He is my spiritual support
그는 나의 영적 지지자입니다
Dimana Xu Yi Nian sekarang?
Dimana Xu Yi Nian 세카랑?
I let go
나는 놓아주었다
The further you go the better
더 멀리 갈수록 더 좋아집니다.
never come back
다시는 돌아오지 않아
Cheng Nuo, please.
쳉 누오(Cheng Nuo) 씨, 제발요.
For the sake of our two long-time brothers,
오랜 시간 함께해온 두 형제를 위해,
Leave it alone.
그대로 두십시오.
don't let him go
그를 보내지 마세요
Sun Yao
쑨 야오
Didn’t you say that too?
당신도 그렇게 말하지 않았나요?
Appreciate the people around you
주변 사람들을 소중히 여기세요
I beg you
부탁드립니다
don't let him go
그를 보내지 마세요
great
엄청난
an idea
아이디어
Itu Xu Yinian
이투 쉬 이니안
Didn't I let you go?
내가 당신을 보내지 않았나요?
Why are you back?
왜 돌아왔나요?
I see people with bright eyes coming
눈이 밝은 사람들이 다가오는 걸 보니
I'm worried something happened to you
너한테 무슨 일이라도 생긴 것 같아 걱정돼
Nona Xu Yinian
노나 쉬이니안
Are you willing to marry Sun Yao?
쑨야오와 결혼할 의향이 있나요?
in sickness and health
질병과 건강에
poor or rich
가난하거나 부자
for life
평생 동안
never leave
결코 떠나지
you want
당신이 원하는
I'm ready
난 준비됐어